Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- England
  - Catnach Press (U-Z), ca. 1813-1885
    - Young Edward the gallant Hussar. The fight. Young Edward the gallant Hussar. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, & 3, Monmouth-cou, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c208; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Young Napoleon: or, The bunch of roses. Adventures of little Mike. Young Napoleon: or, The bunch of roses. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2 & 3, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c209; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Young Napoleon: or, The bunch of roses. Adventures of little Mike. Adventures of little Mike. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2 & 3, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c209; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Young widow. The banks of sweet primroses. The banks of sweet primroses. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, Monmouth-court, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c210; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Young widow. The banks of sweet primroses. The young widow. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, Monmouth-court, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c210; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chubb, W. P., ca. 1825
    Printed in London, England. Oversize item.
    - Protestants song. The Protestants song. London, England; Printed by W. P. Chubb, 63, Long Lane, West Smithfield, [1825]., Shelfmark: chubb1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 38 × 26 cm. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Coatsworth, John, ca. 1842-1882
    Printed in Hull, England.
    - Hurrah for Garibaldi! Hurrah for Garibaldi!. Hull, England; Coatsworth, Printer, 51, Savile-Street, Hull, [between 1842 and 1882]., Shelfmark: 4.17.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 21 × 13 cm. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cruttwell, Richard, 1808
    Printed in Bath, England. Oversize item.
    - Bath Catch Club Bath Catch Club, Bath Catch-club: Ladies' night, January 1, 1808. Bath, England; Printed by Richard Cruttwell, St. Jame's-Street, Bath, 1808., Shelfmark: Crutt1; 1 sheet ([2] p.); 41 × 21 cm. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Curtis, H., 18--
    - Couple in a mess. A couple in a mess. London, England; Printed for the author H. Curtis, Pheasant Court, Gray's Inn Lane, [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:13:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Disley, Henry, ca. 1860-1883
    - Bear it like a man. Bear it like a man. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:4:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bloom is on the rye. Fitzball, Edward, 1792-1873, The bloom is on the rye. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:5:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 16 × 8 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Cast aside. The little church round the corner. The little church round the corner. London, England; Disley, 57, High-street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:9:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Cast aside. The little church round the corner. Cast aside. London, England; Disley, 57, High-street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:9:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Come to the old oak tree. Devereaux, L. (Leonardus), Come to the old oak tree. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:12:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 16 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Come to the old oak tree. Devereaux, L. (Leonardus), Come to the old oak tree. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3:12:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 14 × 8 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Crooskeen [i.e. Cruiskeen] lawn. Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890, Crooskeen [i.e. Cruiskeen] lawn. Bloomsbury, England; Henry Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles. W.C., [1860]., Shelfmark: 3:14:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 17 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Dreadful murder of a wife and six children. Disley, Henry, The dreadful murder of a wife and six children. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 3.18.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Foreigners in England. The foreigners in England. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 4.6.18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Great Shah of Persia. The great Shah of Persia. London, England; Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, [1873]., Shelfmark: 4.13.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Have you seen the claimant, the big fat man. Have you seen the claimant, the big fat man. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 4.15.1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John Barleycorn. John Barleycorn. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John Bull's nothing more. Paul Jones. Paul Jones. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John Bull's nothing more. Paul Jones. Perry, Frederick C., John Bull's nothing more / written by F. C. Perry. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Last Valentine day. Last Valentine day. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 8 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - My motto. What I said to Sally. What I said to Sally. London, England; Disley, Printer, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - My motto. What I said to Sally. My motto. London, England; Disley, Printer, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: D4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Nothing to do with me. Paddy Carey's ball. Nothing to do with me. London, England; Disley, Printer. 57, Higs Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:3:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Nothing to do with me. Paddy Carey's ball. Paddy Carey's ball. London, England; Disley, Printer. 57, Higs Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:3:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Red cross of England: the flag of the brave. Lowlands of Holland. The red cross of England: the flag of the brave. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:12:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Red cross of England: the flag of the brave. Lowlands of Holland. Lowlands of Holland. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:12:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Riding on a donkey. Riding on a donkey. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:13:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Rigs and sprees of the town. Hill, William, Rigs and sprees of the town. London, England; H. Disley, Prin[t]er, 57, High Street, St. Giles [L]ondon. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:13:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 29 × 11 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sheffield prentice. Sheffield prentice. London, England; H. Disley, 57, High-street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 6:18:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sitting by the fireside. I'd choose to be a baby. I'd choose to be a baby. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London. W.C., [1875]., Shelfmark: 8:1:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sitting by the fireside. I'd choose to be a baby. Sitting by the fireside. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London. W.C., [1875]., Shelfmark: 8:1:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Soldier's letter to his sweetheart! The soldier's letter to his sweetheart!. London, England; Henry Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:1:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sparkling moselle. Happier days gone by. Happier days gone by. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:3:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Sparkling moselle. Happier days gone by. Sparkling moselle. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:3:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Wait for the waggon. Knauff, George P., Wait for the waggon. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:12:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 22 × 8 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - We are coming sister Mary. Work, Henry C. (Henry Clay), 1832-1884, We are coming sister Mary. London, England; Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:12:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - We were boys together. Meet me in the morning. Morris, George Pope, 1802-1864, We were boys together. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57 High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:12:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - We were boys together. Meet me in the morning. Meet me in the morning. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57 High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:12:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Wedding day! Wedding day!. London, England; Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:12:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Wife's dream. Becket, Thomas …, 1843-1918, The wife's dream. London, England; H. D[i]sley, Printer, 57, High Street, St Giles, London. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:14:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - William and Harriet. William and Harriet. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High-street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:15:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - William of the waggon train. William of the waggon train. London, England; H. Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, London. W.C., [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:15:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Willie, we have missed you. Foster, Stephen Collins, 1826-1864, Willie, we have missed you. London, England; Disley, Printer, 57, High Street, St. Giles, [between 1860 and 1883]., Shelfmark: 8:15:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Evans, John, ca. 1799-1820
    - Answer to Oh! Cruel. The answer to Oh! Cruel. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long Lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 3:2:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Banks of Inverary. The banks of Inverary. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long Lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 3:3:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Butcher's daughter's policy: or, The lustful lord well fitted. The butcher's daughter's policy: or, The lustful lord well fitted. London, England; Printed by John Evans 42, Long-Lane, West-smithfield, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 3:8:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 22 × 34 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Can't you love whom you please. Can't you love whom you please. London, England; London: Printed by J. Evans, Long-lane, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 3:8:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Dennis M'Phane. Dennis M'Phane. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 3:16:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Hey for the life of a soldier. Hey for the life of a soldier. London, England; Printed by J. Evans, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 4.16.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Honest grocer. Lane, S., The honest grocer. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 4.17.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Jessy, the flow'r o'Dumblain. Tannahill, Robert, 1774-1810, Jessy, the flow'r o'Dumblain. London, England; Printed by J. Evans, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: Evans1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Margate steam yacht. The Margate steam yacht. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: Evans2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Oh! Cruel. Oh! Cruel. London, England; Evans, printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 6:3:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Poor little sailor boy. The soldier's boy. The soldier's boy. London, England; Evans, printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 6:8:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Poor little sailor boy. The soldier's boy. Poor little sailor boy. London, England; Evans, printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 6:8:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Robin's petition. The robin's petition. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 6:14:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Thorn. Burns, Robert, 1759-1796, The thorn. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 8:7:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 23 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Unhappy lovers' tragedy. The unhappy lovers' tragedy. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 8:10:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Woodpecker. Moore, Thomas, 1779-1852, The woodpecker. London, England; Evans, Printer, Long-lane, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: 8:16:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 23 × 9 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Evans, John (Oversize), ca. 1799-1820
    - Lamentable ballad of the tragical end of a gallant lord and virtuous lady: together with the untimely death of their two children. A lamentable ballad of the tragical end of a gallant lord and virtuous lady: together with the untimely death of their two children. London, England; Printed and sold by John Evans, 42, Long Lane, West Smithfield, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: Evans3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 38 cm. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Ulster tragedy. The Ulster tragedy. London, England; Printed by J. Evans & Son, Long-lane, West-smithfield, London, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: o10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 37 × 26 cm. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Yarmouth tragedy: or, The constant lovers. The Yarmouth tragedy: or, The constant lovers. London, England; John Evans, Printer, 42, Long-lane, West smithfield, [between 1799 and 1820]., Shelfmark: o12; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 37 × 25 cm. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Evans, W., 18--
    - Woodman spare that tree. Morris, George Pope, 1802-1864, Woodman spare that tree. London, England; London W. Evans & Co. 22 Warwick Square, Paternoster Row, [18--]., Shelfmark: 8:16:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ford, John, 18--
    Printed in Chesterfield, England.
    - Johnny Armstrong's death, and all his brave men. Johnny Armstrong's death, and all his brave men. Chesterfield, England; Chesterfield: Printed by John Ford, where Travellers &c. may be serv'd, [18--]., Shelfmark: Ford1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 21 × 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Fordyce, W. S., ca. 1828-1837
    - John Barleycorn triumphant: or, The teetotallers in the dumps. Jessie, the flower o'Dumblane. John Barleycorn triumphant: or, The teetotallers in the dumps. London, England; Fordyce, Printer, 48, Dean Street, Newcastle, [between 1828 and 1837]., Shelfmark: Fordy1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - John Barleycorn triumphant: or, The teetotallers in the dumps. Jessie, the flower o'Dumblane. Tannahill, Robert, 1774-1810, Jessie, the flower o' Dumblane. London, England; Fordyce, Printer, 48, Dean Street, Newcastle, [between 1828 and 1837]., Shelfmark: Fordy1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - My Grandfather's days. My Grandfather's days. London, England; Printed & sold by W. & T. Fordyce, Newcastle & Hull. To be had also of J. Whinham & Co. Scotch- st. Carlisle, [ca. 1840]., Shelfmark: Fordy2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Trip to the harvest. A trip to the harvest. Newcastle, England; Fordyce, Printer, 48, Dean Street, Newcastle, [between 1828 and 1837]., Shelfmark: 8:9:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Gitton family, ca. 1824-1834
    Printed in Bridgnorth, England.
    - New song, written expressly for the occasion, and sung with the greatest applause, by Mr. Hallam, at the opening of the New Theatre, Bridgnorth on Saturday evening, December 11th, 1824. Hallam, Mr., A new song, written expressly for the occasion, and sung with the greatest applause, by Mr. Hallam, at the opening of the New Theatre, Bridgnorth on Saturday evening, December 11th, 1824. Bridgnorth, England; Gitton, Jun. Printer, [1824]., Shelfmark: 6:2:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 39 × 22 cm. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The good old days of Adam and Eve / as sung with the most unbounded applause, (during the last theatrical season,) by Mr. Hallam, of the Bridgnorth Theatre. Hudson, Thomas, The good old days of Adam and Eve. Bridgnorth, England; G. Gitton, Printer, Bridgnorth, [between 1824 and 1834?]., Shelfmark: 4.14.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 28 × 23 cm. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gower & Smart, 18--
    Printed in Wolverhampton, England.
    - Song. Song. Wolverhampton, England; Gower & Smart, Wolverhampton, [18--]., Shelfmark: 8:2:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 22 × 12 cm. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Green, 18--
    - Court martial at Windsor! The court martial at Windsor. London, England; Green, Printer, London, [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:13:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Harkness, ca. 1840-1866
    Printed in Preston, England.
    - Cot where I was born. Johnny Gallagher. The cot where I was born. [Preston], [England], [between 1840 and 1866]., Shelfmark: 3:13:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cot where I was born. Johnny Gallagher. Johnny Gallagher. [Preston], [England], [between 1840 and 1866]., Shelfmark: 3:13:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Harrild, Robert, 1814
    - Grand entertainment. The grand entertainment. London, England; [Printed and sold by R. Harrild, 20, Great Eastcheap], [1814]., Shelfmark: 4.12.22; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 30 × 23 cm. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Harris, G. F., ca. 1793-1805
    Printed in Gloucester, England.
    - John Bull: a song, on the threatened invasion, being an introduction to "God save the King". Harris, Joseph, John Bull: a song, on the threatened invasion, being an introduction to "God save the King". London, England; G. F. Harris, Printer, Glocester, [between 1793 and 1805]., Shelfmark: Harris1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 22 × 12 cm. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Harris, William, 18--
    - Bloody gardener. The bloody gardener. Birmingham, England; William Harris, Printer, Deritend, Birmingham, [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:5:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hazard, S., ca. 1795
    - Carpenter: or, The danger of evil company. More, Hannah, 1745-1833, The carpenter: or, The danger of evil company. Bath, England; Sold by S. Hazard, (Printer to the Cheap Repository for Religious and Moral Tracts) at Bath; by J. Marshall, at the Cheap Repositories No. 17, Queen- Street, Cheap-side, and No. 4, Aldermary Church-Yard; R. White, Piccadilly, London…, [1795]., Shelfmark: Haz1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 41 × 24 cm. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - King or a consul?: a new song to the tune of Derry down. More, Hannah, 1745-1833, A king or a consul?: a new song to the tune of Derry down. Bath, England; Bath: Printed and sold by S. Hazard: sold also by Messrs. Rivingtons, St. Paul's Church-Yard; Hatchard, Piccadilly, London; James, Wine-street, Bristol; and by all the booksellers in the United Kingdom, [1795]., Shelfmark: Haz2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 36 × 25 cm. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Roguish miller: or, Nothing got by cheating. A true ballad. More, Hannah, 1745-1833, The roguish miller: or, Nothing got by cheating. A true ballad. Bath, England; Sold by S. Hazard, Printer to the Cheap Repository for Religious and Moral Tracts) at Bath; by J. Marshall, at the Cheap Repositories No. 17, Queen- Street, Cheap-side, and No. 4, Aldermary Church-Yard, London; and by all booksellers, newsmen and hawkers.., [1795]., Shelfmark: Haz3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 41 × 25 cm. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Heggett, T., 18--
    - Jenny Jones: a favourite Welsh melody. Dicky Dolus and his wife. Jenny Jones: a favourite Welsh melody. London, England; T. Heggett, Printer, Durham, [18--]., Shelfmark: Hegg1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Jenny Jones: a favourite Welsh melody. Dicky Dolus and his wife. Dicky Dolus and his wife. London, England; T. Heggett, Printer, Durham, [18--]., Shelfmark: Hegg1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hensen, G., 18--
    Printed in Northampton, England.
    - Answer to the cavalier. I'm a flirt. I'm a flirt. Northampton, England; Henson, Printer, and Publisher, 81, Bridge Street, Northampton. Sold also by J. Taylor, Town Crier, Aylesbury, Bucks, [18-- ]., Shelfmark: 3:2:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Answer to the cavalier. I'm a flirt. Answer to the cavalier. Northampton, England; Henson, Printer, and Publisher, 81, Bridge Street, Northampton. Sold also by J. Taylor, Town Crier, Aylesbury, Bucks, [18-- ]., Shelfmark: 3:2:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Cottager's daughter. The sailor's courtship. The sailor's courtship. Northampton, England; Henson, Printer and Publisher, 81, Bridge Street, Northampton - Sold also by J. Taylor, Town Crier, Aylesbury, Bucks, [18-- ]., Shelfmark: 3:13:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 4, Folder 9)